earnblogger.com 2014-12-15

# Privacy - Earn Blogger

At www.earnblogger.com, the privacy of our users or visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.earnblogger.com and how it is used.

**Log File:**

Like many other Web sites and blogs, [www.earnblogger.com](http://www.earnblogger.com/ "Make Money Online") makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ€™s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**User Information:**

Earnblogger.com may allow some visitors to become an author or user by completing an online form. We consider authors or users as our members, from whom we collect Personal Information that includes data such as a Userâ€™s name, email address, website name (if any), username and password. Users and authors are responsible for keeping all Personal Information current and may change any previously entered information on their account management page. We never sell or rent email address or other personally identifiable information of our users and authors.

We also collect some information such as IP address, name, email address and website (if any) from our visitors, when they give comments on our articles. In this case the visitor’s name and website URL will be visible to all along with the respective comment(s). But, we never reveal, sell or rent the visitor’s IP address and email address to any third-party.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

Earnblogger.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Third Party Advertisers and Links to Third Party Websites:**

The website may include advertisements from third-party companies which may include links to third party websites. The advertisements placed by these companies are not affiliated, owned, maintained or updated by the Company. The third-party ad servers or ad networks use their own technology to deliver the advertisements that appear on [www.earnblogger.com](http://www.earnblogger.com/ "Make Money Online"). They automatically receive your IP address when you view advertisements delivered by those services. Our advertising partners may also use cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. Earnblogger.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.earnblogger.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual web browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie:**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Revisions to this Policy:**

The owner of this blog reserves the right to revise, change, amend, alter or modify (â€œUpdateâ€) this Privacy Policy and its other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user or visitor, is responsible for periodically checking for any Updates of this Privacy Policy by re-visiting this page and by using the â€œrefreshâ€ button on the userâ€™s browser. Any Updates supersede any prior versions immediately upon posting on the page. If the user or visitor does not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, or any updated terms hereto, his/her sole remedy is to not use the website.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info (at) earnblogger.com.
